<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Neunzehn (Japan) [b].zip</path>
    <name>19: Neunzehn</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Neunzehn (Japan) [b].png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Neunzehn (Japan) [b].png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>The heir to the throne is shared by four brave people: Darius, Simon, Thales, and Sonia. The 19 gods of Olympus left behind an omnipotent stone to the great emperor Achilles, who has ordered a search to be conducted for the stone. You take the role of one of these four in an effort to find the stone on the island before the rest, waging war with opponent armies to prevent them from finding it first.nn19 is somewhat unique among turn based strategy games, in that turns are taken in real time, following rules that are reminiscent of the Japanese chess-like game known as Shogi. The game takes place on an overworld map, on which players take turns moving troops. When opposing troops vi for the same location, the game switches to a zoomed-in combat screen, showing each individual member of the opposing forces. While the story of the game revolves around finding a stone, there is no actual stone to discover. Your only goal is to wipe out the armies of the other three opponents.</desc>
    <releasedate>19880304T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Soft Pro International</developer>
    <publisher>Soft Pro International</publisher>
    <genre>Strategy</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Ai Senshi Nicol (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Ai Senshi Nicol</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Ai Senshi Nicol (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Ai Senshi Nicol (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating>1</rating>
    <desc>Help the brave inventor Nicol rescue his kidnapped girlfriend Stella from a Demon Bull King from the planet Dairass in this overhead action game. Control Nicol through 7 continents as he recovers 3 pieces on each level to his dimensional transporter invention that the Demon King stole and encased in diamonds. You&apos;ll blast away at various minions and avoid treacherous terrain while exploring multiple floors of each continent searching out the diamonds to be re-united with Stella and defeat the evil Demon King!</desc>
    <releasedate>19870424T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Shooter, Action, Action / Adventure</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Ai Senshi Nicol (Japan) [b].zip</path>
    <name>Ai Senshi Nicol</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Ai Senshi Nicol (Japan) [b].png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Ai Senshi Nicol (Japan) [b].png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating>1</rating>
    <desc>Help the brave inventor Nicol rescue his kidnapped girlfriend Stella from a Demon Bull King from the planet Dairass in this overhead action game. Control Nicol through 7 continents as he recovers 3 pieces on each level to his dimensional transporter invention that the Demon King stole and encased in diamonds. You&apos;ll blast away at various minions and avoid treacherous terrain while exploring multiple floors of each continent searching out the diamonds to be re-united with Stella and defeat the evil Demon King!</desc>
    <releasedate>19870424T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Shooter, Action, Action / Adventure</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Aki to Tsukasa no Fushigi no Kabe (Japan) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Aki to Tsukasa no Fushigi no Kabe</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Aki to Tsukasa no Fushigi no Kabe (Japan) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Aki to Tsukasa no Fushigi no Kabe (Japan) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Aki to Tsukasa no Fushigi no Kabe is an unlicensed hentai game that&apos;s basically solo table tennis where you hit certain parts of a wall to reveal a girl in an erotic pose.</desc>
    <releasedate>19880915T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Super Pig</developer>
    <publisher>New System House Oh!</publisher>
    <genre>Adult, Puzzle-Game</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Akumajou Dracula (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Akumajou Dracula</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Akumajou Dracula (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Akumajou Dracula (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Transylvania enjoyed a century of peace thanks to the legendary hero, Christopher Belmont, a vampire hunter who vanquished Count Dracula one hundred years earlier with a holy whip named Vampire Killer. While the Easter celebration carried on with a grand carnival, evil men gathered in a monastery at the edge of the village and conducted a black mass to resurrect Count Dracula.

The men succeeded in bringing their master back. A bolt of lightning enveloped the monastery where they held the rite, signaling the resurrection of Count Dracula. When the Count returned, his Castle, which had fallen one hundred years prior, reappeared in Transylvania, and his legions of loyal minions reformed.

Simon Belmont, the descendant of Christopher Belmont, knew that as a member of the Belmont Clan and the current wielder of the Vampire Killer whip, it was his duty to bring peace and stability back to Transylvania by destroying Dracula.</desc>
    <releasedate>19860926T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Akumajou Dracula (Japan) (v1.2) [b].zip</path>
    <name>Akumajou Dracula</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Akumajou Dracula (Japan) (v1.2) [b].png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Akumajou Dracula (Japan) (v1.2) [b].png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Transylvania enjoyed a century of peace thanks to the legendary hero, Christopher Belmont, a vampire hunter who vanquished Count Dracula one hundred years earlier with a holy whip named Vampire Killer. While the Easter celebration carried on with a grand carnival, evil men gathered in a monastery at the edge of the village and conducted a black mass to resurrect Count Dracula.

The men succeeded in bringing their master back. A bolt of lightning enveloped the monastery where they held the rite, signaling the resurrection of Count Dracula. When the Count returned, his Castle, which had fallen one hundred years prior, reappeared in Transylvania, and his legions of loyal minions reformed.

Simon Belmont, the descendant of Christopher Belmont, knew that as a member of the Belmont Clan and the current wielder of the Vampire Killer whip, it was his duty to bring peace and stability back to Transylvania by destroying Dracula.</desc>
    <releasedate>19860926T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Dracula II - Noroi no Fuuin (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Akumajou Dracula II: Noroi no Fuuin</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Dracula II - Noroi no Fuuin (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Dracula II - Noroi no Fuuin (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>The game&apos;s setting takes place seven years after the original Castlevania. The prologue begins when Simon visits his family&apos;s resting ground. His back is critically injured from his last encounter with Dracula in the previous game. He suddenly feels someone&apos;s presence, and turns to see a young woman standing within the mist. She tells him that a curse was placed upon him by Dracula during their last battle, and that he does not have long to live. The woman continues to say that the curse can be undone if he resurrects Dracula himself. She further explains that Dracula&apos;s body was split into five different parts after his defeat seven years ago, and Simon must recover these and bring them to the ruins of Dracula&apos;s castle. There, he must seal Dracula and defeat him. Before disappearing, the unknown woman says she cannot guarantee that this will destroy Dracula permanently.

Dracula II - Noroi no Fuuin (Lit. &quot;Dracula II: The Seal of the Curse&quot;) is an action-adventure game produced by Konami. It was originally released for the Family Computer Disk System in Japan in 1987, and for the NES in North America in 1988. It is the second Castlevania title released for the NES, following the original Castlevania. Set in 1698, seven years after the events of the first installment, the player once again assumes the role of vampire hunter Simon Belmont, who is on a journey to undo a curse placed on him by Dracula at the end of their previous encounter. Small differences exist between the Japanese version and the American version. Specifically the Japanese version takes advantage of the expanded FM processing capabilities of the FDS hardware to produce better sound, but it contains load scenes when entering or exiting any town or mansion. The FDS version also has three save slots instead of the NES password system.</desc>
    <releasedate>19870827T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Action / Adventure, Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/All Night Nippon Super Mario Brothers (Japan) (Promotion Cart).zip</path>
    <name>All Night Nippon Super Mario Brothers</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/All Night Nippon Super Mario Brothers (Japan) (Promotion Cart).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/All Night Nippon Super Mario Brothers (Japan) (Promotion Cart).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>All Night Nippon - Super Mario Bros. was a promotional item given out as a contest prize by the Japanese radio show &quot;All Night Nippon&quot; to celebrate its twentieth year on the air. It combines levels from both Super Mario Bros 1 &amp; 2 and also changes graphics of items and their placements as well as graphics of enemies and mushroom retainers to members of the show.</desc>
    <releasedate>19861022T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Nintendo</developer>
    <publisher>Fuji Television Network</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Platform</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Apple Town Monogatari - Little Computer People (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Apple Town Monogatari : Little Computer People</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Apple Town Monogatari - Little Computer People (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Apple Town Monogatari - Little Computer People (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>A version of Little Computer People for Nintendo&apos;s Family Computer Disk System version, published in Japan by DOG (a subsidiary of Square). Based on the original game by Activision.

Unlike previous versions of Little Computer People, the playable character is a girl wearing a pink dress and bow in her hair. The rooms of the house are also in a different configuration, featuring an outdoor balcony on the top floor. When the game is first played, a name for the character is chosen at random from a preprogrammed list. There are no winning conditions on this game you basically watch and interact with the girl in various ways. However, Apple Town Story lacks many of the features found in other versions of Little Computer People.</desc>
    <releasedate>19870403T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Square Soft</developer>
    <publisher>Disk Original Group (DOG)</publisher>
    <genre>Simulation</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Armana no Kiseki (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Armana no Kiseki</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Armana no Kiseki (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Armana no Kiseki (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>A magic red jewel known as the Almana is stolen from an unnamed village. A thief runs off with the jewel and turns the entire village into stone. The player takes the role of Kaito a hero who resembles Indiana Jones and must travel through six cavernous levels in search of the lost jewel. Kaito&apos;s main source of transportation is unique. Besides just walking and jumping, like most platform games, he must also use a special grappling hook to reach platforms that are too high. To make things a little more difficult, the grappling hook can only be launched from a diagonal direction and not just straight above.</desc>
    <releasedate>19870811T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Aspic - Majaou no Noroi (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Aspic : Majaou no Noroi</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Aspic - Majaou no Noroi (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Aspic - Majaou no Noroi (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Aspic is the sequel to one of Xtalsoft&apos;s earlier games, Lizard. Aspic begins right where Lizard ends. The player obtains the Book of Truth, which is needed to break the curse on the princess. He returns to the king only to find that the princess is missing. Three days prior, a wizard appeared and informed the king that there was another way to save the princess, so the king entrusted the princess&apos;s life to the wizard. Now that you&apos;ve returned, the king begs you to find out what&apos;s become of the wizard and the princess.</desc>
    <releasedate>19880331T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Xtalsoft</developer>
    <publisher>Bothtec</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Bio Miracle Bokutte Upa (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Bio Miracle Bokutte Upa</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Bio Miracle Bokutte Upa (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Bio Miracle Bokutte Upa (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Upa is the prince of a magical kingdom and the most recent in a line of brave fighters. One day, though, he broke an urn containing the spirit of Zai, an incredibly evil goatish demon who takes the life force of the kingdom&apos;s adults and kidnaps all the babies - except for Upa, who is given a magical rattle by a fairy who was trapped in the urn along with Zai. And so, in order to save his kingdom, Upa crawls into action... He will navigating side scrolling stages with platforms and can inflate enemies by hitting them with his rattle for use as temporary platforms or to throw at adversaries.</desc>
    <releasedate>19880422T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Platform</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Bishoujo SF Alien Battle (Japan) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Bishoujo Alien Battle</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Bishoujo SF Alien Battle (Japan) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Bishoujo SF Alien Battle (Japan) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Bishoujo SF Alien Battle is an unlicensed Family Computer Disk System video poker game The game features two disks, one with the game on it, and one containing the reward picture for beating the game. You play as a young Japanese schoolgirl, who must defeat an alien super-mind in video poker to just be raped by its tentacle-waving henchman, instead of brutally murdered.</desc>
    <releasedate>19901019T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Hacker International</developer>
    <publisher>Hacker International</publisher>
    <genre>Adult, Playing cards</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Bishoujo Control (Japan) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Bishoujo Control</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Bishoujo Control (Japan) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Bishoujo Control (Japan) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating>0.4</rating>
    <desc>Combining all the fun of an arcade shoot&apos;em&apos;up with all the excitement of watching pretty girls, Girl&apos;s Control puts you in a spaceship, battling hordes of enemies flying downwards. All that flies is not an enemy, though; you can also shoot at blocks that, when shot, make up a picture of a pretty girl on the right of the screen. Picking up bonuses in the shape of the signs for &quot;pretty girl&quot; powers up your weapon. When all pieces of the picture are picked up, you are given a chance to enjoy the picture at your own pace before progressing to the next level (and the next girl). 

The gameplay can be spiced up by upgrading your spaceship into a much more &quot;phallic&quot; configuration, with bullets looking like big sperm, while the enemies come in the shape of scissors, mouths, pants and syringes. Your ship can also gain a condom shield. Whereas the MSX version starts off like a more normal shooter, progressively becoming more vulgar, this is the default mode in the Famicom version.
</desc>
    <releasedate>19901001T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Wild</developer>
    <publisher>Wild</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Shoot&apos;em up / Vertical, Adult, Shoot&apos;em Up</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Bishoujo Mahjong Club (Japan) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Bishoujo Mahjong Club</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Bishoujo Mahjong Club (Japan) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Bishoujo Mahjong Club (Japan) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>An adult mahjong game with two girls to choose from and a &quot;battle mode&quot;. At odd intervals of points, you are treated to the girl of choice stripping, which equates to an unnecessarily long musical number, slow text filling in her speech bubble, and then a flash before she reappears minus one article of clothing. The girl can win back clothes if your score drops.</desc>
    <releasedate>19880601T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Super Pig</developer>
    <publisher>Mimi-Pro</publisher>
    <genre>Adult, Mahjong, Casino, Asiatic board game</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Bishoujo Sexy Derby (Japan) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Bishoujo Sexy Derby</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Bishoujo Sexy Derby (Japan) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Bishoujo Sexy Derby (Japan) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Bishoujo Sexy Derby is a horse-racing game developed by Super Pig and published by Hacker International for the Famicom Disk System in 1988. The point of the game is to race horses for money, and the girls take off various articles of clothing when you get more and more money.</desc>
    <releasedate>19880912T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Super Pig</developer>
    <publisher>Hacker International</publisher>
    <genre>Casino, Sports with Animals, Horses race, Adult</genre>
    <players />
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Bishoujo Shashinkan - Studio Cut (Japan) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Bishoujo Shashinkan I: Studio Cut</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Bishoujo Shashinkan - Studio Cut (Japan) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Bishoujo Shashinkan - Studio Cut (Japan) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Bishoujo Shashinkan I: Studio Cut is a life simulation game developed by HARD and published by Phoenix for the Famicom Disk System in 1987.
Your task is to photograph pretty girls in various situations. You are given a choice of point-and-shoot, single lens reflex and a pro camera. 
You are only given a few chances per shoot to get the right exposure, or you will just see a miscoloured picture flash briefly. Judging the exposure correctly grants you a picture of the girl, often in a surprising state of undressing, whereafter you progress to even more erotic poses. Later stages raise the difficulty level, forcing you to use the SLR, and later the meter-less pro camera.</desc>
    <releasedate>19870109T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>HARD</developer>
    <publisher>Phoenix</publisher>
    <genre>Adult, Simulation</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Cocona World (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Cocona World</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Cocona World (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Cocona World (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>You control a young witch who wanders throughout various parts of the kingdom. There are many animal inhabitants to interact with, some of which are good and some of which are evil. There are also a number of activities to perform and mini-games to play. Over time, the witch will request that certain activities be performed. If they are not performed within a certain time period, the player receives a penalty. Over time, the character&apos;s mood and strength will drop. If both of these are never restored and drop to zero, the game is over. This game was only released in Japan, and has never been translated into English.</desc>
    <releasedate>19870410T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>SOFEL Co., Ltd.</developer>
    <publisher>SOFEL Co., Ltd.</publisher>
    <genre>Adventure</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Deep Dungeon II - Yuushi no Monshou (Japan) (v1.1) [b].zip</path>
    <name>Deep Dungeon II - Yuushi no Monshou</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Deep Dungeon II - Yuushi no Monshou (Japan) (v1.1) [b].png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Deep Dungeon II - Yuushi no Monshou (Japan) (v1.1) [b].png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>In the time the last game, strange things have happened at the town of Dorl. A proclamation was made that Ruu has been resurrected. The people gathered in the temple to pray, until the swordsman Ral had been summoned by the heavens to enter the castle and fight Ruu.

Like it&apos;s prequel the game takes place in a 3D dungeon crawling environment only this time there is a tower to conquer as well as a dungeon. Battles also happen in real-time so if you idle too long you will quickly be attacked. However once you reach certain levels enemies will no longer randomly attack you.</desc>
    <releasedate>19870529T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Humming Bird Soft</developer>
    <publisher>Disk Original Group (DOG)</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Dirty Pair - Project Eden (Japan) [b].zip</path>
    <name>Dirty Pair : Project Eden</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Dirty Pair - Project Eden (Japan) [b].png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Dirty Pair - Project Eden (Japan) [b].png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Kei and Yuri, two cute space investigators, are the heroines of this side-scrolling action game by Bandai and based on the popular animation series Dirty Pair. This was released along with the movie Project Eden though it doesn&apos;t follow the plot of the actual movie all that well. Also the game is known for it&apos;s incredible difficulty.</desc>
    <releasedate>19870328T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Daiei Seisakusho</developer>
    <publisher>Bandai</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Donkey Kong (Japan) (Disk Writer).zip</path>
    <name>Donkey Kong</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Donkey Kong (Japan) (Disk Writer).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Donkey Kong (Japan) (Disk Writer).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>You are Mario, and that big old gorilla, Donkey Kong, has run off with your girlfriend. It&apos;s up to you to struggle up those ladders and balance on those beams to rescue your lady fair. She&apos;s held captive at the very top. But Donkey Kong is not ready to give her up so easily. He&apos;s tossing barrels and fireballs at you at every turn. It&apos;s up to you to outmaneuver that wily ape. Good luck, your lady awaits!</desc>
    <releasedate>19880408T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Nintendo</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Platform</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Donkey Kong (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Donkey Kong</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Donkey Kong (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Donkey Kong (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>You are Mario, and that big old gorilla, Donkey Kong, has run off with your girlfriend. It&apos;s up to you to struggle up those ladders and balance on those beams to rescue your lady fair. She&apos;s held captive at the very top. But Donkey Kong is not ready to give her up so easily. He&apos;s tossing barrels and fireballs at you at every turn. It&apos;s up to you to outmaneuver that wily ape. Good luck, your lady awaits!</desc>
    <releasedate>19880408T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Nintendo</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Platform</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Donkey Kong Jr. (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Donkey Kong Jr.</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Donkey Kong Jr. (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Donkey Kong Jr. (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Mario has gone mad! He&apos;s turned the tables on Donkey Kong and locked him in a cage. It&apos;s up to you, as Donkey Kong Jr., to rescue your father by stealing Mario&apos;s set of keys. But it won&apos;t be easy. You&apos;ll have to fight off ape-eating Snapjaws, jump onto moving islands and break through a jungle of vines to get to the keys that will free Donkey Kong. Can you handle the action? Because this off-the-wall monkey business will have you going bananas!</desc>
    <releasedate>19880719T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Nintendo</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Platform</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Donkey Kong Jr. (Japan) (Disk Writer).zip</path>
    <name>Donkey Kong Jr.</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Donkey Kong Jr. (Japan) (Disk Writer).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Donkey Kong Jr. (Japan) (Disk Writer).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Mario has gone mad! He&apos;s turned the tables on Donkey Kong and locked him in a cage. It&apos;s up to you, as Donkey Kong Jr., to rescue your father by stealing Mario&apos;s set of keys. But it won&apos;t be easy. You&apos;ll have to fight off ape-eating Snapjaws, jump onto moving islands and break through a jungle of vines to get to the keys that will free Donkey Kong. Can you handle the action? Because this off-the-wall monkey business will have you going bananas!</desc>
    <releasedate>19880719T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Nintendo</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Platform</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Dr. Chaos - Jigoku no Tobira (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Dr. Chaos : Jigoku no Tobira</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Dr. Chaos - Jigoku no Tobira (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Dr. Chaos - Jigoku no Tobira (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Dr. Chaos is a side-scrolling action adventure developped by Marionette and published by Pony Canyon. The genius scientist Dr Ginn Chaos has gone missing. Before his disappearance, he was actively working in his large mansion on a device allowing access to alternate dimensions. Armed only with a knife, his brother decides to look for him and ultimately unveil the mystery behind the incident. Something obviously went terribly wrong with Dr. Chaos&apos;s experiment, and the goal of the game is to locate all the eleven dimensional warp-zones hidden within the mansion, as well as assembling a powerful laser gun, the only weapon capable of taking down the last boss.</desc>
    <releasedate>19860619T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Marionette Co., Ltd.</developer>
    <publisher>Pony Canyon, Inc.</publisher>
    <genre>Action / Adventure, Action, Platform</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Dr. Chaos - Jigoku no Tobira (Japan) [b].zip</path>
    <name>Dr. Chaos : Jigoku no Tobira</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Dr. Chaos - Jigoku no Tobira (Japan) [b].png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Dr. Chaos - Jigoku no Tobira (Japan) [b].png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Dr. Chaos is a side-scrolling action adventure developped by Marionette and published by Pony Canyon. The genius scientist Dr Ginn Chaos has gone missing. Before his disappearance, he was actively working in his large mansion on a device allowing access to alternate dimensions. Armed only with a knife, his brother decides to look for him and ultimately unveil the mystery behind the incident. Something obviously went terribly wrong with Dr. Chaos&apos;s experiment, and the goal of the game is to locate all the eleven dimensional warp-zones hidden within the mansion, as well as assembling a powerful laser gun, the only weapon capable of taking down the last boss.</desc>
    <releasedate>19860619T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Marionette Co., Ltd.</developer>
    <publisher>Pony Canyon, Inc.</publisher>
    <genre>Action / Adventure, Action, Platform</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Druid - Kyoufu no Tobira (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Druid : Kyoufu no Tobira</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Druid - Kyoufu no Tobira (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Druid - Kyoufu no Tobira (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Druid is an action game inspired by the arcade hit Gauntlet. As the eponymous hero, your job is to destroy four magic skulls hidden over eight levels.The game is presented in a top-down view. The druid walks around the terrain seeking out the staircase that leads to the next level. On the way, he is harassed by hordes of monsters that come out of every direction and attack him, decreasing his health. To defend himself, the druid can use the spells of water, fire or electricity to toss projectiles. However, these magical weapons have limited ammo.</desc>
    <releasedate>19880303T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Jaleco</developer>
    <publisher>Jaleco</publisher>
    <genre>Adventure, Action / Adventure, Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Egger Land (Japan) [b].zip</path>
    <name>Eggerland</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Egger Land (Japan) [b].png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Egger Land (Japan) [b].png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>The Eggerland series is better known outside of Japan as The Adventure of Lolo series.The game is often referred to as &quot;Syodai&quot;, or the &quot;first one&quot;. The game is a remake of &quot;Meikyuu Shinwa&quot; (Eggerland 2; lit. &quot;Labyrinth Myth&quot;) for the MSX2 Home Computer System with updated graphics and different music. Furthermore, in this remake the location of some special rooms was swapped, and a final boss battle was introduced.In this Eggerland, Lolo must navigate his way through a non-linear series of rooms, the majority of which occupy a 10x10 arrangement along the main floor of a castle. Many rooms have more than one exit for Lolo to choose from, and a map can be collected along the way to provide the player with information about where he or she is, and what rooms have already been visited. Secret entrances to hidden chambers must be found so that keys can be collected, enabling the player to explore deeper into the castle.</desc>
    <releasedate>19870129T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
    <publisher>HAL Laboratory</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Puzzle-Game</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Emi-chan no Moero Yakyuuken! (Japan) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Emi-chan no Moero Yakyuuken!</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Emi-chan no Moero Yakyuuken! (Japan) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Emi-chan no Moero Yakyuuken! (Japan) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>It&apos;s a strip janken game. Janken&apos;s just a fancy Japanese word for rock-paper-scissors I think, but janken&apos;s easier to type. The whole ?strip? part of the game is, for every match you lose, you take off an article of clothing. Woo! For every match you win, Emi (the girl you play against) takes off an article of clothing. WOO! For every match you tie, Emi puts back on an article of clothing. WHAT?! Yeah, it&apos;s a pirate game, no one said it had to be fair.nnnnWhat&apos;s even more unfair is, once you get Emi down to like, four articles of clothing, you have to win three times against various barnyard animals. Win three times against a barnyard animal, win against Emi, she loses another article of clothing. Win three MORE times against another barnyard animal, win against Emi, she loses another article of clothing. So yeah, the match is pretty easily stacked in her favor, wouldn&apos;t you say? Too bad you don&apos;t have any mammals lying around to protect YOU in your strip janken game.nnnnSo yeah, just use up and down to cycle through the different hands, and hit A to choose what you want. Yeah, really complicated.</desc>
    <releasedate>19871001T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Super Pig</developer>
    <publisher>New System House Oh!</publisher>
    <genre>Adult</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Esper Dream (Japan) (v1.1) [b].zip</path>
    <name>Esper Dream</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Esper Dream (Japan) (v1.1) [b].png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Esper Dream (Japan) (v1.1) [b].png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>This is a story that occurred in the distant village from where you live.
This village was filled with a beautiful, quiet, and mysterious aroma.

However, the villagers suffered from an unexpected tragedy.
The Evil clan called Narcisse tribe, began searching for the magic hidden in our village.

Even worse, they kidnapped the daughter of our mayor, Alice.

Please, go forth and rescue Alice, and bring peace to our land!</desc>
    <releasedate>19870220T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Role playing games</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Exciting Baseball (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Exciting Baseball</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Exciting Baseball (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Exciting Baseball (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>A baseball simulator, Exciting Baseball follows Exciting Billiards and Exciting Basket (better known as Double Dribble in the West) in Konami&apos;s series of sports games for the Famicom Disk System.

Like the others in the Exciting series it&apos;s a straightforward exemplar of its particular sport. It doesn&apos;t have the flair of the original two Exciting games, as it never had an Arcade antecedent.</desc>
    <releasedate>19871208T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Sports, Sports / Baseball</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Exciting Basket (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Exciting Basket</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Exciting Basket (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Exciting Basket (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Exciting Basket (Known in the US as Double Dribble) was a basketball arcade game developed and released in 1987 by Konami. Much of the game&apos;s popularity came from its animation sequences showing basketball players performing slam dunks.Players can choose from one of four teams: Boston, Chicago, Los Angeles and New York. There is no difference in skill level or abilities between the teams. Since there is no NBA license, no team names or player names are used, however, the teams wear the same color of their NBA counterparts (Boston wears green, Chicago red, etc.).</desc>
    <releasedate>19870724T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Sports, Sports / Basketball</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Exciting Billiard (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Exciting Billiard</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Exciting Billiard (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Exciting Billiard (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Exciting Billiard is a billiard simulation game developed and published by Konami for the Family Computer Disk System in 1987. It was the first of Konami&apos;s &quot;Exciting Sports&quot; series produced for the Nintendo Famicom, similar to Namco&apos;s own &quot;Family Sports&quot; label. Exciting Billiard offers players four modes of play. Break Shot is a single player only mode, where the player competes against other pool hustlers for money, attempting to earn enough money to graduate to higher and more impressive venues with increasing amounts of money on each bet. The remaining three modes can be played with one to four players at a time (human or computer controlled), with each players&apos; progress capable of being saved to disk.</desc>
    <releasedate>19870626T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Sports, Sports / Pool</genre>
    <players>4</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Exciting Soccer - Konami Cup (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Exciting Soccer : Konami Cup</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Exciting Soccer - Konami Cup (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Exciting Soccer - Konami Cup (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Players select one of the various soccer teams, and aim to become the best team in the league. Each team possesses different levels of kick strength, endurance, dribbling technique, defensive skill, and luck. They are set at the beginning of the game, but can be enhanced through training. During play, the view of the field is a bird&apos;s eye view, with either goal located at the far top and bottom sections of the field. Although this game is considered a relatively minor release, it&apos;s ending BGM entitled &quot;Seaside Memory&quot; is highly revered.</desc>
    <releasedate>19880216T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Sports, Sports / Soccer</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Exciting Soccer - Konami Cup (Japan) [b].zip</path>
    <name>Exciting Soccer : Konami Cup</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Exciting Soccer - Konami Cup (Japan) [b].png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Exciting Soccer - Konami Cup (Japan) [b].png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Players select one of the various soccer teams, and aim to become the best team in the league. Each team possesses different levels of kick strength, endurance, dribbling technique, defensive skill, and luck. They are set at the beginning of the game, but can be enhanced through training. During play, the view of the field is a bird&apos;s eye view, with either goal located at the far top and bottom sections of the field. Although this game is considered a relatively minor release, it&apos;s ending BGM entitled &quot;Seaside Memory&quot; is highly revered.</desc>
    <releasedate>19880216T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Sports, Sports / Soccer</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Falsion (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Falsion</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Falsion (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Falsion (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Humanity has colonized most planets in our galaxy, the Milky Way, and they now look towards expanding their reach by using an experimental travel technology called &quot;Hyperzone Drive&quot;. However, a race of aliens who have already mastered that technology are currently invading planets at a quick pace, closing in on our solar system. The invaders attack humanity&apos;s colony on Pluto and conquer it with little resistance, since human civilization doesn&apos;t have the technology to defend itself.

The human organization responsible for the space program, the &quot;United Space Force&quot;, decides to use the yet-untested &quot;Hyperzone Drive&quot; in order to send ships that will directly attack the armies of the invading aliens. However, the new technology proves hard to control, and only one of the ships manages to survive the trip: Falsion.</desc>
    <releasedate>19871012T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Shooter</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Famicom Grand Prix II - 3D Hot Rally (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Famicom Grand Prix II : 3D Hot Rally</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Famicom Grand Prix II - 3D Hot Rally (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Famicom Grand Prix II - 3D Hot Rally (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>The second game in the Famicom Grand Prix series. In a departure from its predecessor, Famicom Grand Prix II features a behind-the-car view similar to Outrun and Rad Racer. Rather than consisting of a handful of short tracks, 3D Hot Rally provides three long tracks consisting of a variety of different terrain types giving the feel of an actual rally race. Each track has multiple routes to the finish line, requiring you to find the best path to victory. The game features three cars to choose from: the speedy Kattobi coupe, the balanced Yonque truck, or the rugged Monster buggy.



In order to complete a race, players must reach each checkpoint within a certain time limit. If the limit is crossed too late, time is subtracted from their bank. If the time bank is depleted, the race is over. Successfully reaching a checkpoint before the time limit is reached banks extra time. Players can also collect exclamation marks scattered throughout the tracks. Collecting enough exclamation marks to fill the dash meter allows temporary access to the hot dash, a fifth gear that greatly increases speed. Before each race, you&apos;re asked to place a repair point somewhere on the track, allowing you to repair any damage done to your car, so long as you pick a route that leads you past that checkpoint. Taking too much damage puts you out of the race.



As the name implies, 3D Hot Rally allows you to use the Famicom 3D System glasses to give the race a real feeling of depth. It also challenged players to submit their best times via Famicom Disk Fax kiosks located in various stores for a chance to win a Disk-kun stationary set.</desc>
    <releasedate>19880414T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Nintendo</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Race, Driving</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Final Commando - Akai Yousai (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Final Commando - Akai Yousai</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Final Commando - Akai Yousai (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Final Commando - Akai Yousai (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Your brothers-in-arms are hostages behind enemy lines, and you&apos;re their only hope for freedom. But the firepower you&apos;ll face to rescue them is awesome. Cannons, tanks, submarines and snipers will blast you with horrific crossfire, while jet fighters zero in from above. To defend yourself, you control the army&apos;s advanced all-terrain attack jeep, with its arsenal of guided missiles and incendiary grenades. Of course these are merely tools, and to save your countrymen you&apos;ll need more than a handful of gunpowder. You&apos;ll need a pocketful of miracles, and the ferocity of a wild Jackal!</desc>
    <releasedate>19880502T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Shooter, Shoot&apos;em Up</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Fire Rock (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Fire Rock</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Fire Rock (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Fire Rock (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Fire Rock is an action game developed for the Famicom Disk System by System Sacom, and published in Japan by Use in 1988. The design of the game is credited to Mark Flint. In the game, the player controls what appears to be a cave man, whose goal is to navigate a series of item filled caverns in an effort to locate the boss of the level, defeat it, and then locate the door which leads to the next level. The game is commonly sited as having very poor controls, often requiring the player to grab hold of a wall, and very slowly climb it by holding up and tapping jump repeatedly. Other issues include a very low jump that places more platforms and items out of reach, and a difficult time bringing the character back under control if he starts to slip. This game was not released outside of Japan.</desc>
    <releasedate>19860620T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>System Sacom</developer>
    <publisher>Use Corporation</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Ginga Denshou - Galaxy Odyssey (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Ginga Denshou : Galaxy Odyssey</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Ginga Denshou - Galaxy Odyssey (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Ginga Denshou - Galaxy Odyssey (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Ginga Denshou - Galaxy Odyssey is a game developed for the Family Computer Disk System by Wave Jack, and published by Imagineer in 1986. Unlike most games for the FDS, Galaxy Odyssey did not come with just a disk and an instruction booklet. Among the contents found in the large box, were an audio cassette tape and a book recounting the game&apos;s story.The game itself is quite unusual as well. It features a blend of vertical shooting gameplay mixed with more Zelda-like exploration sequences. As the pilot of a ship, you could dock with certain dungeon entrances, and take a shuttle down to the ground to explore and search for items. Searching around isn&apos;t easy at first, since you run out of oxygen fairly quickly, and that starts to drain your life, of which you start out with three bars.To win the game, you must find the medicine needed to rescue the people who are suffering from a disease in your home area. To do so, you must collect warp codes, and translate alien codes, and blast off from one dungeon location to travel to another. The game&apos;s text is in Japanese, and has never been translated to another language.</desc>
    <releasedate>19861106T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Imagineer</developer>
    <publisher>Imagineer</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Golf (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Golf</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Golf (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Golf (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>A port of the Nintendo Famicom game to the Famicom Disk System.

Golf is a sports-simulation video game released in 1984. The golfer is a mustached man who resembles Mario.

The player one character wears a white shirt and shoes with blue pants and uses a white ball, while the player two character wears a red shirt and shoes with black pants and uses a red ball.

The user must first decide whether to play single stroke play or the two player selections of doubles stroke play or match play. The user is then placed at the tee of the first hole of eighteen.</desc>
    <releasedate>19860221T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Nintendo</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Sports, Sports / Golf</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Golf (Japan) (v1.1).zip</path>
    <name>Golf</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Golf (Japan) (v1.1).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Golf (Japan) (v1.1).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>A port of the Nintendo Famicom game to the Famicom Disk System.

Golf is a sports-simulation video game released in 1984. The golfer is a mustached man who resembles Mario.

The player one character wears a white shirt and shoes with blue pants and uses a white ball, while the player two character wears a red shirt and shoes with black pants and uses a red ball.

The user must first decide whether to play single stroke play or the two player selections of doubles stroke play or match play. The user is then placed at the tee of the first hole of eighteen.</desc>
    <releasedate>19860221T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Nintendo</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Sports, Sports / Golf</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Golf, The - Bishoujo Classic (Japan) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Golf : Bishoujo Classic, The</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Golf, The - Bishoujo Classic (Japan) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Golf, The - Bishoujo Classic (Japan) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>An adult game in which you play golf, upon doing well enough you will see various girls undress.</desc>
    <releasedate />
    <developer>Hacker International</developer>
    <publisher>Hacker International</publisher>
    <genre>Adult, Sports, Sports / Golf</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Family Computer Golf Japan Course (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Golf : Japan Course</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Family Computer Golf Japan Course (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Family Computer Golf Japan Course (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>An update of sorts to Golf. Players get to take control of Nintendo&apos;s mascots Mario and Luigi (in the 2 player game) and play over 18 holes of golf on courses modeled after real courses in Japan.

Players can choose to either try their skills in match play or stroke play. Match play involves two golfers trying to win the most holes. They win holes by getting the better score than their competitor. Stroke play differs as it just involves the golfer trying to get the best score possible by completing each hole in as few strokes as possible.

When on the golf course, players can choose the club they want to use, adjust the speed and strength (from a 1 to 3 scale) of their swing, and aim in the direction they want to hit the ball. Hitting the ball involves the use of a meter with an icon that goes back and forth, which gauges the distance the ball is hit. Players can take a step back from the tee and take practice swings so they can get into a rhythm using this meter.

This game also contained a now defunct feature where players could record their personal information and their best scores and then bring the game disk to a Disk Fax machine. Inserting the disk into this machine would fax over the player&apos;s information to Nintendo&apos;s headquarters. This information was used for a contest. Being selected a contest winner would award the player with a golden colored disk version of this game. This golden disk version of the game contained an exclusive course that was not present on the original version of this game.</desc>
    <releasedate>19870221T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Sports, Sports / Golf</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Family Computer Golf U.S. Course (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Golf: U.S. Course</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Family Computer Golf U.S. Course (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Family Computer Golf U.S. Course (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>A slightly updated companion title to Golf - Japan Course released just a few months earlier. The graphics are more updated and the gameplay is a little more advanced as well. Players get to take control of Nintendo&apos;s mascots Mario and Luigi (in the 2 player game) and play over 18 holes of golf on courses modeled after real courses in the USA.

Players can choose to either try their skills in match play or stroke play. Match play involves two golfers trying to win the most holes. They win holes by getting the better score than their competitor. Stroke play differs as it just involves the golfer trying to get the best score possible by completing each hole in as few strokes as possible.

When on the golf course, players can choose the club they want to use, adjust the speed and strength (from a 1 to 3 scale) of their swing, and aim in the direction they want to hit the ball. Hitting the ball involves the use of a meter with an icon that goes back and forth, which gauges the distance the ball is hit. Players can take a step back from the tee and take practice swings so they can get into a rhythm using this meter.

This game also contained a now defunct feature where players could record their personal information and their best scores and then bring the game disk to a Disk Fax machine. Inserting the disk into this machine would fax over the player&apos;s information to Nintendo&apos;s headquarters. This information was used for a contest. Being selected a contest winner would award the player with a golden colored disk version of this game. This golden disk version of the game contained an exclusive course that was not present on the original version of this game.</desc>
    <releasedate>19870614T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Sports, Sports / Golf</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Hayama Reiko no Date de Blackjack (Japan) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Hayama Reiko no Date de Blackjack</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Hayama Reiko no Date de Blackjack (Japan) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Hayama Reiko no Date de Blackjack (Japan) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>An adult poker game by Hacker International in which you will play a girl in poker. Upon winning enough you will have interactions with her in which she slowly undresses.</desc>
    <releasedate>19900518T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Hacker International</developer>
    <publisher>Hacker International</publisher>
    <genre>Adult, Casino</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Hikari Shinwa - Parthenon no Kagami (Japan) (v1.1) [b].zip</path>
    <name>Hikari Shinwa : Palthena no Kagami</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Hikari Shinwa - Parthenon no Kagami (Japan) (v1.1) [b].png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Hikari Shinwa - Parthenon no Kagami (Japan) (v1.1) [b].png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>In a time where humans and gods coexisted in harmony, the kingdom of Angel Land was ruled by two goddesses, Palutena the Goddess of Light and Medusa the Goddess of Darkness. While Palutena administered the light and helped the mortals cultivate their crops, Medusa despised the mortals and used the darkness to destroy their crops and turn the mortals into stone. Enraged, Palutena transformed Medusa into a hideous monster and banished her into the dark Underworld.

But Medusa would not go quietly. She assembled an army of monsters and evil spirits of the underworld to conquer Palutena&apos;s home, the Palace in the Sky. War erupted and Medusa&apos;s minions overwhelmed Palutena&apos;s army, eventually imprisoning the Goddess of Light. Medusa then seized the Three Sacred Treasuresthe Mirror Shield, the Arrow of Light, and the Wings of Pegasusand gave them to her most powerful minions.

Defeated and imprisoned, Palutena&apos;s only hope was to seek the help of Pit, a young angel trapped in the Underworld. Using the last of her strength, she sent Pit a magical bow. Thus, Pit set out on a quest to escape the Underworld, retrieve the Sacred Treasures that would help him defeat Medusa, and rescue Palutena and restore peace to Angel Land.

The original Famicom Disk System versions feature save slots, unlike the North American version which uses a password system (known in-game as &quot;Sacred Words&quot;). As with Metroid, the FDS version of Kid Icarus also features higher-quality music and sound effects that take advantage of the system&apos;s additional sound channels.</desc>
    <releasedate>19861219T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Nintendo</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Platform</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Ice Hockey (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Ice Hockey</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Ice Hockey (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Ice Hockey (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>The play and mechanics of Ice Hockey are mostly similar to that of ice hockey in real life. The objective for both team is to hit a black puck with a hockey stick that each player carries into the opponent&apos;s goal. Teams are made up of five players including the goaltender, as opposed to six in real life. Players wear ice skates, which are used to skate across the icy arena. Each game is made up of three periods, with the victory going to the team who has the most points at the end of the game. At the beginning, two opposing players from each team face off in the middle of the rink. There are three kinds of players - the first is fast, weak, and feeble, but is good at the face-off; the second is average in all qualities, and the third is slow and poor at the face-off, but very powerful, both in body checking and shooting strength. The arena is similarly designed to a real-world ice hockey arena. The arena is coated in ice, with a goal on either side of the arena. There are a variety of marked areas, including the goal line that the puck must cross to score, the attacking/defending zone which is situated closely to each goal, the face-off spot, the neutral spot, and others. Each side of the arena has exactly the same design. If two opposing players fight for the puck for a certain amount of time, other players join into the fight, resulting in the player from the losing team in the fight to be put in the penalty box for a period of time.</desc>
    <releasedate>19980121T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Nintendo</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Sports, Sports / Hockey</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Karin no Tsurugi (Japan) [b].zip</path>
    <name>Kalin no Tsurugi</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Karin no Tsurugi (Japan) [b].png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Karin no Tsurugi (Japan) [b].png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Monsters have appeared in the once peaceful land of Alitania, and the people have fallen into terror. The king&apos;s orders have fallen upon you, the bravest knight of Alitania.

&quot;The fate of the country hangs by a thread. It may be possible to save the country with Gladrif&apos;s magic, but he is nowhere to be found. Therefore, I want you to search for him! Find Gladrif, defeat the monsters, and restore peace to this land once again!&quot;</desc>
    <releasedate>19871002T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Xtalsoft</developer>
    <publisher>Disk Original Group (DOG)</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Karate Champ (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Karate Champ</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Karate Champ (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Karate Champ (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>The player assumes the role of a karate competitor and fights against another player or the computer. Using two joysticks, players can execute a number of moves.

Gameplay consists of a two dimensional fight between Karate characters wearing white and red gi, followed by various bonus rounds for the successful player. This pattern repeats itself in the next, more challenging round set against a new background. Unlike most later fighter-type games, there are no health bar or hit points. A hit successfully landed ends the round and earns the player or his opponent either one point or half point (along with a numeric score for the top ten but this has no effect on winning a match per se). The first to score two points is the winner. If the player loses a battle, the game ends. The game also featured some early speech synthesis, in which the judge would call out such phrases as &quot;Fight!&quot; or &quot;Winner!&quot; It&apos;s also spoken in Japanese in the Japanese version.</desc>
    <releasedate>19880722T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Data East</developer>
    <publisher>Data East</publisher>
    <genre>Fight</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Kieta Princess (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Kieta Princess</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Kieta Princess (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Kieta Princess (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>The Kingdom of Rabia&apos;s princess goes missing during a visit to Japan, surrounding the investigation of the medicine to an &quot;epidemic dementia,&quot; known as &quot;Oninofuguri&quot;, and the prevention of its importing. The player takes the role of a detective determined to unravel the mystery of the missing princess Kilala, in this RPG style adventure game. Yasuko Tomita served as the model of one of the characters. Certain telephone numbers would appear, which, if called, would provide the player with a hint, spoken by Yasuko Tomita.

In order to track down Kobayashi, the criminal protagonist, you must visit five different towns and collect information. Neary every house and building can be entered, which was unique for its time. The game also features a high degree of freedom, allowing you to visit restaurants for a bite, or a Dojo to train, or to hunt for vegetation to sell for money, while you are looking for the princess.

Another introduced concept that was novel for its time was the notion of day and night changing the appearance of the city. During the evening, you may encounter a street gang, and they may open fire on you, although you can defend yourself with a revolver. However, if over 20 innocent people are gunned down, you will be arrested and sent to the police station where you must pay a fine and return to the starting point.

The degree of difficult throughout the game is considered quite high, with very few hints to help you out, while other hints are misleading. For example, one hint suggests that you if you sleep over night at a particular crossroad in a city, you will get a key item, but this hint is false. Although you are supposedly a detective, you never actually get to accuse anyone of a crime.</desc>
    <releasedate>19861220T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Imagineer</developer>
    <publisher>Wave Jack</publisher>
    <genre>Adventure</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Monitor Puzzle Kineko, The - Kinetic Connection (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Kinetic Connection</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Monitor Puzzle Kineko, The - Kinetic Connection (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Monitor Puzzle Kineko, The - Kinetic Connection (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>A Disk Writer only release, The Monitor Puzzle Kinetic Connection - Kineco II is the sequel in which new puzzles are introduced. Like it&apos;s prequel the game challenges player to piece together ten images in a jigsaw puzzle like fashion. However, every piece is exactly the same size, and the images on the pieces move. Rather than using the shape of the edges to determine what pieces fit next to one another, you must use the animation on the pieces to determine their arrangement. When each puzzle begins, the pieces are also oriented randomly, so you may be required to flip them vertically or horizontally in order to complete the puzzle. There are 10 different animations, and you can choose between dividing the images into 16, 24, or 48 distinct pieces before attempting to solve the puzzle. Obviously, the fewer pieces, the easier it is to solve.</desc>
    <releasedate>19861128T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Tamtex</developer>
    <publisher>Irem</publisher>
    <genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Knight Move (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Knight Move</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Knight Move (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Knight Move (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>The game is based around the concept of how a knight piece is moved in the game of chess. The player controls a knight chess piece that is constantly jumping and must continually choose which of the possible legal moves to make before the knight lands back on the board.

When the knight lands on any square on the board, it turns from white to light teal. Landing there again, turns it dark teal. Landing there yet again destroys the square altogether, leaving a hole that the player must avoid. Falling in a hole will result in a game over. Consecutively creating several holes results in a chain increasing the player&apos;s score in differing increments.

At the beginning of each &quot;round&quot;, a heart is placed somewhere on the board. A heart (or multiple hearts) must be collected to advance to the next round, which thereby replaces all holes on the board with new white squares and places a new heart somewhere on the board. Depending on the game mode, hearts will sometimes move themselves every few jumps of the knight.

The player can also gather a small amount of extra points, at any time, by holding the A button and speeding up the knight&apos;s movement. The main objective in Knight Move is to continue this cycle, despite the increasing game speed, and reach the highest score possible.

The game also includes a simultaneous 2 player versus mode similar to the single player modes.</desc>
    <releasedate>19900605T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>JV Dialog</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Kobayashi Hitomi no Hold Up (Japan) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Kobayashi Hitomi no Hold Up</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Kobayashi Hitomi no Hold Up (Japan) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Kobayashi Hitomi no Hold Up (Japan) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Kobayashi Hitomi no Hold Up is a puzzle/shooting for adults developed and published by Hacker International for the Famicom Disk System in 1990.
In this solo game, you play a game of Hold Up with the beautiful model Kobayashi Hitomi.</desc>
    <releasedate>19900807T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Hacker International</developer>
    <publisher>Hacker International</publisher>
    <genre>Puzzle-Game, Adult</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Legend of Zelda 2, The - Link no Bouken (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Link no Bouken : The Legend of Zelda 2</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Legend of Zelda 2, The - Link no Bouken (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Legend of Zelda 2, The - Link no Bouken (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Link no Bouken - The Legend of Zelda 2 is the second installment in The Legend of Zelda series, published by Nintendo for the Nintendo Entertainment System. It was originally released in Japan on the Famicom Disk System less than a year after the release of The Legend of Zelda. 

The Adventure of Link is a direct sequel to the original The Legend of Zelda, and again involves the protagonist Link on a quest to save Princess Zelda -- who is not the same Princess from the first game, but another member of the royal family by the same name, who was placed under a sleeping spell a long time ago. The Adventure of Link&apos;s emphasis on side-scrolling and RPG-style elements, however, was a significant departure from its predecessor and has given it a reputation as the &quot;black sheep&quot; of the Zelda series. It is arguably the hardest Zelda game. Despite this reputation, the game was highly successful and introduced many elements that would become commonplace in future Zelda games.</desc>
    <releasedate>19870114T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Nintendo</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Legend of Zelda 2, The - Link no Bouken (Japan) (v1.1).zip</path>
    <name>Link no Bouken : The Legend of Zelda 2</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Legend of Zelda 2, The - Link no Bouken (Japan) (v1.1).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Legend of Zelda 2, The - Link no Bouken (Japan) (v1.1).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Link no Bouken - The Legend of Zelda 2 is the second installment in The Legend of Zelda series, published by Nintendo for the Nintendo Entertainment System. It was originally released in Japan on the Famicom Disk System less than a year after the release of The Legend of Zelda. 

The Adventure of Link is a direct sequel to the original The Legend of Zelda, and again involves the protagonist Link on a quest to save Princess Zelda -- who is not the same Princess from the first game, but another member of the royal family by the same name, who was placed under a sleeping spell a long time ago. The Adventure of Link&apos;s emphasis on side-scrolling and RPG-style elements, however, was a significant departure from its predecessor and has given it a reputation as the &quot;black sheep&quot; of the Zelda series. It is arguably the hardest Zelda game. Despite this reputation, the game was highly successful and introduced many elements that would become commonplace in future Zelda games.</desc>
    <releasedate>19870114T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Nintendo</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Lipstick #.1 - Lolita Hen (Japan) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Lipstick #1 : Lolita Hen</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Lipstick #.1 - Lolita Hen (Japan) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Lipstick #.1 - Lolita Hen (Japan) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc />
    <releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Mimi-Pro</developer>
    <publisher>Hacker International</publisher>
    <genre>Puzzle-Game, Adult</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Lipstick #.2 - Joshi Gakusei Hen (Japan) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Lipstick #2 : Joshi Gakusei Hen</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Lipstick #.2 - Joshi Gakusei Hen (Japan) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Lipstick #.2 - Joshi Gakusei Hen (Japan) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc />
    <releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Mimi-Pro</developer>
    <publisher>Hacker International</publisher>
    <genre>Puzzle-Game, Adult</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Lipstick #.3 - OL Hen (Japan) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Lipstick #3 : OL Hen</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Lipstick #.3 - OL Hen (Japan) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Lipstick #.3 - OL Hen (Japan) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc />
    <releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Mimi-Pro</developer>
    <publisher>Hacker International</publisher>
    <genre>Puzzle-Game, Adult</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Lipstick #.4 - Hakui no Tenshi Hen (Japan) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Lipstick #4 : Hakui no Tenshi Hen</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Lipstick #.4 - Hakui no Tenshi Hen (Japan) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Lipstick #.4 - Hakui no Tenshi Hen (Japan) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc />
    <releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Mimi-Pro</developer>
    <publisher>Hacker International</publisher>
    <genre>Puzzle-Game, Adult</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Lipstick #.5 - Stewardess Hen (Japan) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Lipstick #5 : Stewardess Hen</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Lipstick #.5 - Stewardess Hen (Japan) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Lipstick #.5 - Stewardess Hen (Japan) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc />
    <releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Mimi-Pro</developer>
    <publisher>Hacker International</publisher>
    <genre>Puzzle-Game, Adult</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Deep Dungeon - Madou Senki (Japan) [b].zip</path>
    <name>Madou Senki : Deep Dungeon</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Deep Dungeon - Madou Senki (Japan) [b].png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Deep Dungeon - Madou Senki (Japan) [b].png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>The town of Dorl has an infestation of demons who currently reside in the castles dungeon after a portal to the underworld was opened. The emperor of the underworld, Emperor Ruu, commanded his demons to raid the town to steal its treasure and during this ransacking the demons also managed to take Princess Etna&apos;s soul away too, leaving her in a comatose state. Many brave adventurers have entered the underground dungeon to try and reclaim her soul from this demon king, but none have returned successfully yet. So now it&apos;s up to the player to succeed where others have failed and put an end to the Emperor Ruu and also recover Princess Etna&apos;s soul.</desc>
    <releasedate>19861218T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Humming Bird Soft</developer>
    <publisher>Disk Original Group (DOG)</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Meikyuu Jiin Dababa (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Meikyuu Jiin Dababa</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Meikyuu Jiin Dababa (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Meikyuu Jiin Dababa (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>The game takes place in India, where a young man&apos;s significant-other is kidnapped by an evil wizard. He must then tackle the four areas of the labyrinth temple of Dababa to rescue her.

In order to accomplish this task, the player cannot simple move across the floor. Rather, the player and all of the enemies hop from one square tile to another, throughout the game. In a majority of stages, the player must uncover the seals which will unlock the door to the next stage by leaping on to the particular tiles which keep the seals concealed. Not every door will take the player forward, however, as some doors are trick doors that may take the player to a previous stage. In some stages, the player must simply survive the onslaught of enemies, while in others, the player is racing against the clock.</desc>
    <releasedate>19870529T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Sailor Fuku Bishoujo Zukan Vol. 1 (Japan) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Meimon Joshi Kousei Sailor Fuku Bishoujo Zukan #1 Meimonnyama no Te Ojousama Joshikou Henn A</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Sailor Fuku Bishoujo Zukan Vol. 1 (Japan) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Sailor Fuku Bishoujo Zukan Vol. 1 (Japan) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>A pornographic action game.</desc>
    <releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Mimi-Pro</developer>
    <publisher>Hacker International</publisher>
    <genre>Adult</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Sailor Fuku Bishoujo Zukan Vol. 3 (Japan) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Meimon Joshi Kousei Sailor Fuku Bishoujo Zukan #3 Meimonn Seijun Ojousama Kouritsu Joshikousei A</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Sailor Fuku Bishoujo Zukan Vol. 3 (Japan) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Sailor Fuku Bishoujo Zukan Vol. 3 (Japan) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc />
    <releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Mimi-Pro</developer>
    <publisher>Hacker International</publisher>
    <genre>Adult</genre>
    <players />
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Sailor Fuku Bishoujo Zukan Vol. 4 (Japan) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Meimon Joshi Kousei Sailor Fuku Bishoujo Zukan #4 Meimonn Seijun Ojousama Kouritsu Joshikousei B</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Sailor Fuku Bishoujo Zukan Vol. 4 (Japan) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Sailor Fuku Bishoujo Zukan Vol. 4 (Japan) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc />
    <releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Mimi-Pro</developer>
    <publisher>Hacker International</publisher>
    <genre>Adult</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Sailor Fuku Bishoujo Zukan Vol. 5 (Japan) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Meimon Joshi Kousei Sailor Fuku Bishoujo Zukan #5 Meimonn Jjunnai Ojousama Shiritsu Kouritsu Joshikousei A</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Sailor Fuku Bishoujo Zukan Vol. 5 (Japan) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Sailor Fuku Bishoujo Zukan Vol. 5 (Japan) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc />
    <releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Mimi-Pro</developer>
    <publisher>Hacker International</publisher>
    <genre>Adult</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Sailor Fuku Bishoujo Zukan Vol. 6 (Japan) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Meimon Joshi Kousei Sailor Fuku Bishoujo Zukan #6 Meimonn Jjunnai Ojousama Shiritsu Kouritsu Joshikousei B</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Sailor Fuku Bishoujo Zukan Vol. 6 (Japan) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Sailor Fuku Bishoujo Zukan Vol. 6 (Japan) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc />
    <releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Mimi-Pro</developer>
    <publisher>Hacker International</publisher>
    <genre>Adult</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Metroid (Japan) (v1.2) [b].zip</path>
    <name>Metroid</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Metroid (Japan) (v1.2) [b].png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Metroid (Japan) (v1.2) [b].png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>It&apos;s you against the evil Mother Brain in the thrilling battle of Metroid! You&apos;re inside the fortress planet Zebes. The planet of endless secret passageways where the Metroid are multiplying. Left alone the Metroid are harmless. But in the wrong hands they could destroy the galaxy. It&apos;s up to you to prevent the Mother Brain that controls Zebes from using the Metroid for evil purposes. But that won&apos;t be easy. You&apos;ll have to use your spacesuit to absorb valuable energy for your search to gain the use of power items like the Ice Beam, Wave Beam, High Jump Boots and Varia. If you survive, it will be you and your acquired powers against the Mother Brain.</desc>
    <releasedate>19860806T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Nintendo</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Adventure</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Michael English Daibouken (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Michael English Daibouken</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Michael English Daibouken (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Michael English Daibouken (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Michael English Daibouken (lit: &quot;Michael&apos;s English Grand Adventure&quot;) is an educational game where the character of Michael, an orange cat, teaches kittens the various letters in the English language as well as some English vocabulary. Michael has to catch floating letters in order to spell out English words, while avoiding the incorrect letters. The game has various different backdrops, including space.

The character of Michael comes from the Japanese serial manga strip &quot;What&apos;s Michael&quot;, created by Makoto Kobayashi which might be considered analogous to Garfield, due to them both being orange cats. It varies between observing goofy pet behavior to more abstract tales of fantasy with anthropomorphized versions of the animal characters.</desc>
    <releasedate>19870619T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Scorpion Soft</developer>
    <publisher>Scorpion Soft</publisher>
    <genre>Puzzle-Game, Educational</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Michael English Daibouken (Japan) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Michael English Daibouken</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Michael English Daibouken (Japan) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Michael English Daibouken (Japan) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Michael English Daibouken (lit: &quot;Michael&apos;s English Grand Adventure&quot;) is an educational game where the character of Michael, an orange cat, teaches kittens the various letters in the English language as well as some English vocabulary. Michael has to catch floating letters in order to spell out English words, while avoiding the incorrect letters. The game has various different backdrops, including space.

The character of Michael comes from the Japanese serial manga strip &quot;What&apos;s Michael&quot;, created by Makoto Kobayashi which might be considered analogous to Garfield, due to them both being orange cats. It varies between observing goofy pet behavior to more abstract tales of fantasy with anthropomorphized versions of the animal characters.</desc>
    <releasedate>19870619T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Scorpion Soft</developer>
    <publisher>Scorpion Soft</publisher>
    <genre>Puzzle-Game, Educational</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Moero TwinBee - Cinnamon Hakase wo Sukue! (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Moero TwinBee : Cinnamon Hakase wo Sukue!</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Moero TwinBee - Cinnamon Hakase wo Sukue! (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Moero TwinBee - Cinnamon Hakase wo Sukue! (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Moero TwinBee can be played by up to three player simultaneously: the first two players control TwinBee and WinBee (the ships from the previous game) using the standard Famicom controllers, whereas the third player controls GwinBee (a green ship) by connecting an additional controller into the console&apos;s expansion port. Unlike the original TwinBee, which only featured vertical-scrolling stages, Stinger adds side-scrolling stages to the mix as well. There are seven stages in the game. Stage 1, 3, and 7 are side-scrolling stages, while the rest are vertical-scrolling stages. The controls remain the same between the two styles of gameplay, with the only difference being that in the side-scrolling segments, the A button shoots hearts over the ship instead of dropping bombs into the ground like the vertical-scrolling segments, which helps the player keep the power-up bells afloat in the side-scrolling stages.</desc>
    <releasedate>19861121T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Shooter, Shoot&apos;em Up</genre>
    <players>3</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Monty on the Run - Monty no Doki Doki Dai Dassou (Japan) [b].zip</path>
    <name>Monty on the Run : Monty no Doki Doki Dai Dassou</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Monty on the Run - Monty no Doki Doki Dai Dassou (Japan) [b].png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Monty on the Run - Monty no Doki Doki Dai Dassou (Japan) [b].png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Monty no Doki Doki Dai Dassou  (Monty&apos;s heart pounding great escape), also known as Monty on the Run, is an action game developed for the Famicom Disk System by Jaleco in 1987. This game was the product of Jaleco acquiring the rights to license and publish a hit game from the European computer market titled Monty on the Run. However, unlike a similar previous effort with Knight Lore which stays close to the original source, Jaleco changed the game entirely for unknown reasons.nnIn Monty no Doki Doki Dai Dassou , Monty is a human being who has escaped from a penitentiary. Still dressed in striped convict clothing, Monty is on a mission to clear his name. He must proceed through four levels, each of which contains several hidden tiles. These tiles contain portions of the image of a face. At the end of each level, Monty must jump on to a platform just before the exit. This platform is a direct clue to the proper construction of the collected tiles. There are more tiles than necessary to construct a face, making some tiles extraneous. Only by paying proper attention to this final platform can the player know which face to construct. At the end of the game, the player must properly reconstruct the face of the true criminal before a judge. If the player succeeds, he will earn his freedom and win the game.</desc>
    <releasedate>19870731T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Jaleco</developer>
    <publisher>Jaleco</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Platform</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Idol Hotline - Nakayama Miho no Tokimeki High School (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Nakayama Miho no Tokimeki High School</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Idol Hotline - Nakayama Miho no Tokimeki High School (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Idol Hotline - Nakayama Miho no Tokimeki High School (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>The game&apos;s protagonist enters Tokimeki High School and runs into a girl wearing glasses who looks identical to Miho Nakayama. Though the game is a standard text command-style adventure game similar to the Famicom Tantei Club series, in important scenes, the player is required to select a facial expression in addition to a verbal response. The four expressions (straight face, laughter, sadness, anger) must match the content of the response being given, and any incorrect responses immediately lead to the &quot;game over&quot; screen. This increased the game&apos;s difficulty considerably in comparison to other text adventure games where there were fewer incorrect choices. Some scenes specifically require that the dialogue not match with the expression. For instance, choosing a dialogue expressing joy with a straight face may be the correct choice in a certain situation because it represents a deeper level of emotion and thought on the part of the protagonist. This system allowed the game to simulate a level of complexity resembling actual love relationships, leading to its classification as a dating simulation rather than an adventure game. The game has two different endings, depending on the choices made during the game, and the prizes receivable via the Disk Fax network differed for each ending.</desc>
    <releasedate>19871201T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Square Soft</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Adventure</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Nazo no Kabe - Block Kuzushi (Japan) [b].zip</path>
    <name>Nazo no Kabe : Block Kuzushi</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Nazo no Kabe - Block Kuzushi (Japan) [b].png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Nazo no Kabe - Block Kuzushi (Japan) [b].png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>In the year 30XX, the mankind has exhausted all the metal resources on the Earth, so they had to travel into space in order to find more. They find a planet high in minerals, and they name it Selim.

But soon they discover that there is someone watching, spying on them; it&apos;s some kind of alien race. These aliens find a hole in the humans&apos; main computer and get inside it. The computer, programmed to self-destruct in case of a failure, starts its countdown.

There is only one way to avoid self-destruction, which is entering a 14 digit code into the machine; but these digits are hidden in the walls of the corridors in the complex. Your mission is to find these letters and avoid self-destruction, aboard the &quot;Red Warrior&quot;, and using your only weapon, an energy ball.

Nazo no Kabe - Block Kuzushi  is an Arkanoid clone for the NES, but it&apos;s probably one of the most singular clones. You&apos;ll have to destroy all blocks but also the walls surrounding them, as the 14 letters are spread inside them, apart from killing the alien bosses here and there. In your way, you will find a bizarre mixture of enemies, from alien forms to parts of the body (eyes, lips, skulls...), who will make your game tougher by changing the direction of your ball; but also happier by dropping a sweet variety of power-ups such as the cherries (extra life), the clock (the enemies freeze), a rocket (to throw into the blocks), a fire device (the ball fires missiles), a parachute (slows the ball) an extra ball, or the weirdest of them all, the so-called Konami Man, who will take you to a secret parallel complex with different (and harder) levels.</desc>
    <releasedate>19861213T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Nazo no Kabe - Block Kuzushi (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Nazo no Kabe : Block Kuzushi</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Nazo no Kabe - Block Kuzushi (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Nazo no Kabe - Block Kuzushi (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>In the year 30XX, the mankind has exhausted all the metal resources on the Earth, so they had to travel into space in order to find more. They find a planet high in minerals, and they name it Selim.

But soon they discover that there is someone watching, spying on them; it&apos;s some kind of alien race. These aliens find a hole in the humans&apos; main computer and get inside it. The computer, programmed to self-destruct in case of a failure, starts its countdown.

There is only one way to avoid self-destruction, which is entering a 14 digit code into the machine; but these digits are hidden in the walls of the corridors in the complex. Your mission is to find these letters and avoid self-destruction, aboard the &quot;Red Warrior&quot;, and using your only weapon, an energy ball.

Nazo no Kabe - Block Kuzushi  is an Arkanoid clone for the NES, but it&apos;s probably one of the most singular clones. You&apos;ll have to destroy all blocks but also the walls surrounding them, as the 14 letters are spread inside them, apart from killing the alien bosses here and there. In your way, you will find a bizarre mixture of enemies, from alien forms to parts of the body (eyes, lips, skulls...), who will make your game tougher by changing the direction of your ball; but also happier by dropping a sweet variety of power-ups such as the cherries (extra life), the clock (the enemies freeze), a rocket (to throw into the blocks), a fire device (the ball fires missiles), a parachute (slows the ball) an extra ball, or the weirdest of them all, the so-called Konami Man, who will take you to a secret parallel complex with different (and harder) levels.</desc>
    <releasedate>19861213T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Nazo no Murasame Jou (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Nazo no Murasamejou</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Nazo no Murasame Jou (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Nazo no Murasame Jou (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>In feudal Japan, an evil alien descends upon Murasame castle and takes over a giant statue, which then continues to spread its influence over four neighbouring castles. The samurai apprentice Takamaru is thus summoned to recapture the castles and then take on the alien itself.

Nazo no Murasamejou is a fast-paced action game that has some similarities with The Legend of Zelda, although it is faster and has none of the RPG/Adventure elements. It is also much more linear: You fight through the castles one after the other, with each stage consisting of the path to the castle and the castle itself, where the boss is waiting.

Your have two weapons: (unlimited) shurikens for ranged attacks and a sword for melee combat. The sword is automatically used when you are close enough to an enemy, and it can also be used to deflect enemy shurikens. But since you are constantly under attack by ninjas from all directions and also have only a limited time to finish each stage, the game is still quite hard.</desc>
    <releasedate>19860414T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Nintendo</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Adventure</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Nazoraa Land Dai 2 Gou (Japan) (Nazo Magazine Disk).zip</path>
    <name>Nazoler Land : Dai 2 Gou</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Nazoraa Land Dai 2 Gou (Japan) (Nazo Magazine Disk).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Nazoraa Land Dai 2 Gou (Japan) (Nazo Magazine Disk).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Nazoler Land Dai 2 Gou was the second of three &quot;Magazine Disks&quot; published by Sunsoft for the Famicom Disk System in the middle of 1987. The full title of the disk is Nazo no Magazine Disk Nazoler Land Dai 2 Gou which translates as &quot;Puzzle Magazine Disk Nazoler Land 2nd Issue.&quot; Rather than featuring one game, it contains a collection of 6 games which would be considered &quot;mini-games.&quot; The player selects which game to play from the menu screen.</desc>
    <releasedate>19870612T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sunsoft</developer>
    <publisher>Sunsoft</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Casual Game</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Nazoraa Land Dai 3 Gou (Japan) (Nazo Magazine Disk) [b].zip</path>
    <name>Nazoler Land : Dai 3 Gou</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Nazoraa Land Dai 3 Gou (Japan) (Nazo Magazine Disk) [b].png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Nazoraa Land Dai 3 Gou (Japan) (Nazo Magazine Disk) [b].png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Nazoler Land Dai 3 Gou was the third and final &quot;Magazine Disk&quot; published by Sunsoft for the Famicom Disk System. This last disk was released in 1988. The full title of the disk is Nazo no Magazine Disk Nazoler Land Dai 3 Gou which translates as &quot;Puzzle Magazine Disk Nazoler Land 3rd Issue.&quot; Rather than featuring one game, it contains a collection of 6 games which would be considered &quot;mini-games.&quot; The player selects which game to play from the menu screen.</desc>
    <releasedate>19880311T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sunsoft</developer>
    <publisher>Sunsoft</publisher>
    <genre>Puzzle-Game, Casual Game</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Nazoraa Land Soukan Gou (Japan) (Nazo Magazine Disk) [b].zip</path>
    <name>Nazoler Land : Soukan Gou</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Nazoraa Land Soukan Gou (Japan) (Nazo Magazine Disk) [b].png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Nazoraa Land Soukan Gou (Japan) (Nazo Magazine Disk) [b].png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Nazoler Land Soukan Gou is the first in a series of minigame collections from SunSoft developed especially for Nintendo&apos;s Famicom Disk System peripheral. It was followed by two direct sequels and a quiz-based spin-off.

Nazoler Land Soukan Gou (or Nazoler Land Vol. 1) has eight minigames that the player can select from a menu after loading the game up and switching the disk around. These are:
Rotation Maze

A maze-like puzzle game where a small circular being has to pass through a maze filled with dividers. The player can only pass through these dividers if there is room for it to turn around, otherwise it blocks the player&apos;s progress. The goal is to find the correct path through the maze.
Nazoler Fortune-Telling

Despite using signs of the Zodiac and suggesting a fortune-telling aspect, the game is actually a variant on the classic strategy board game Mastermind: The goal is to find the right combination of Zodiac symbols, and the game will provide hints by reporting whenever the player includes the right symbol, either in the correct place (represented by a solid star) or the wrong place (represented as a hollowed star).
Super Jigsaw

In this game the player simply has to reconstruct an image after pieces of it have been jumbled up. All the player must do is use two cursors to point to the two pieces they wish to switch around. Restoring the image to its initial state completes the challenge.
Save Princess Momoko!

Promoted as the &quot;major feature&quot;, or the most fully-developed of the minigames. The goal is to explore a dungeon in a first-person perspective, similar to classic dungeon crawlers such as Wizardry, Dungeon Master or Shining in the Darkness, while finding items and using the correct items on the right monsters to proceed past them. Encountering these monsters before finding the right item to defeat them causes the player to lose, so there&apos;s a degree of trial and error.
Japan&apos;s Best Surroundings: Ultra Travel Quiz

A quiz based on traveling around Japan and general geographical facts. The player selects which type of transportation (train, plane, etc.) they wish to take and answers questions relating to it.
Famicom Reaction Test

In this simple &quot;game&quot;, two players compete to hit the button on their controller as many times as they can in the short time limit. This test is presented like a Wild West duel.
Extrusion Puzzle

Similar to Super Jigsaw, only the player is sliding blocks around to make a puzzle appear. Pushing one block that&apos;s against an</desc>
    <releasedate>19870206T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sunsoft</developer>
    <publisher>Sunsoft</publisher>
    <genre>Puzzle-Game, Casual Game</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Nazoraa Land Zoukan Gou - Quiz Ou wo Sagase! (Japan) (Nazo Magazine Disk) [b].zip</path>
    <name>Nazoler Land Special!! : Quiz Ou wo Sagase</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Nazoraa Land Zoukan Gou - Quiz Ou wo Sagase! (Japan) (Nazo Magazine Disk) [b].png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Nazoraa Land Zoukan Gou - Quiz Ou wo Sagase! (Japan) (Nazo Magazine Disk) [b].png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Nazoler Land Special!! Quiz Ou wo Sagase (Lit. Puzzle Land Special!! Search for the Quiz King) was a special edition of the Nazoler Land series published by Sunsoft for the Family Computer Disk System at the end of 1987. Unlike the other Nazoler Land disks, this one does not contain a series of different mini-games, but rather a single game focusing on a trivia quiz. The player must visit various locations around Japan in an effort to &quot;battle&quot; various trivia masters, and beat all eight of them in order to claim the title as the Quiz King. The game was only released in Japan, and has never been translated from Japanese. As a result, a high level of Japanese knowledge is required to play this game.</desc>
    <releasedate>19871218T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sunsoft</developer>
    <publisher>Sunsoft</publisher>
    <genre>Quiz</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Family Computer Othello (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Othello</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Family Computer Othello (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Family Computer Othello (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Othello is a conversion of the board game. Each player tries to fill the game board with as many discs of his color as possible. On each turn the player places a disc on the board by selecting a location where the opponents discs will become trapped between two of his discs. The trapped discs are flipped over to the players color. The game ends when the board is filled or time runs out, and the player with the greatest number of his color discs on the board wins. Two players can play against each other, or one player against the computer.</desc>
    <releasedate>19861013T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
    <publisher>Kawada, Co. Ltd</publisher>
    <genre>Strategy, Asiatic board game, Othello</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Professional Mahjong Gokuu (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Professional Mahjong Gokuu</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Professional Mahjong Gokuu (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Professional Mahjong Gokuu (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Professional Mahjong Gokuu is the third game for the Famicom to be based on Mahjong, the competitive tile game popular in China and Japan. It is a four-person version of the game, which is generally how the game is played in real life, though uncommon in simulations during this era due to the additional computing power needed for three AI opponents.

As a &quot;professional&quot; Mahjong game, there is an opportunity to play a mode where the player can gamble on outcomes beforehand. The amount of cash gained or lost is usually based on the quality of the winning hand, but occasionally the player can also make bets to increase their take should they win (though, of course, any money gambled in this way is lost if someone else wins the hand).</desc>
    <releasedate>19861225T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Chat Noir</developer>
    <publisher>ASCII Corporation</publisher>
    <genre>Mahjong, Asiatic board game</genre>
    <players>4</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/ProWres - Famicom Wrestling Association (Japan) [b].zip</path>
    <name>Puroresu Famicom Wrestling Association</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/ProWres - Famicom Wrestling Association (Japan) [b].png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/ProWres - Famicom Wrestling Association (Japan) [b].png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>The player chooses a wrestler with unique skills and presses various combinations of buttons to use different wrestling moves. It is possible to leave the ring; however, a player who does so must re-enter the ring before the referee&apos;s 20-count. Failure to do so results in a loss (via count-out) or a draw (double count-out), if both wrestlers fail to re-enter in time. (Note: The referee&apos;s count is broken only after both wrestlers have re-entered the ring. That is, as long as at least one wrestler is outside the ring, the referee&apos;s count continues. Moreover, it is possible for a wrestler to be counted out while executing a &quot;plancha&quot; if he has crossed the ring ropes by the count of 20.</desc>
    <releasedate>19861013T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Nintendo</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Fight, Sports, Sports / Wrestling</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Risa no Yousei Densetsu (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Risa no Yousei Densetsu</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Risa no Yousei Densetsu (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Risa no Yousei Densetsu (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Risa no Yousei Densetsu (Risa&apos;s Fairy Legend) is a text adventure game developed by Konami, and published for the Famicom Disk System in 1988. In the game, you control a protagonist that you name, but the game also stars Risa Tachibana, a popular Japanese singer around the time of the game&apos;s release. Together with Risa, your goal is to defeat a witch of darkness by obtaining several key items. Six of Risa&apos;s songs are interwoven into the adventure, and the lyrics can provide clues to the proper solution of the game, which is divided into four chapters. At times, a telephone number would appear on the screen, and a telephone service was established for a limited time so that players could call the numbers to get more clues. At times, use of the microphone on the second Famicom controller is required to make progress in the game.</desc>
    <releasedate>19880621T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Adventure</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Samurai Sword (Japan) [b].zip</path>
    <name>Samurai Sword</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Samurai Sword (Japan) [b].png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Samurai Sword (Japan) [b].png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Samurai Sword is an adventure game developed and published by Capcom for the Famicom Disk System in Japan towards the end of 1988. The player is an unnamed hero who is promptly defeated by the game&apos;s antangonist Soron and whisked away before the moment of his demise in order to find a way to counter Soron&apos;s considerable magical might.

While the game may resemble an RPG at first, it is actually a traditional Famicom adventure game, similar to Portopia Renzoku Satsujin Jiken or Princess Tomato in the Salad Kingdom. The player can select from a set of commands for the hero to follow such as looking around, talking to NPCs, picking up items and so on. While there are battles, they can only be resolved by finding the right command (often the right spell) rather than the standard RPG method of exchanging blows governed by various statistics.</desc>
    <releasedate>19881115T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Capcom</developer>
    <publisher>Capcom</publisher>
    <genre>Adventure</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Smash Ping Pong (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Smash Ping Pong</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Smash Ping Pong (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Smash Ping Pong (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Smash Ping Pong simulates the game of ping-pong or table tennis in a remarkably different manner than prior simulations of any variety of tennis. Rather than putting the emphasis on precise control and placement of the paddle in order to return the ball, the emphasis is on timing and strategic control of the ball&apos;s speed and trajectory. The player sees no other on-screen representation of themselves beyond a hand holding a paddle. The hand and the paddle automatically move left and right to match the horizontal position of the ball. Players need only concern themselves with the timing of their paddle swing, and the style of swing to use. Players can choose between three different swings, along with the choice of forehand or backhand. 

The Famicom Disk System conversion was developed by Konami, and published directly by Nintendo as Smash Ping Pong. As a result,Konami&apos;s penguin mascot Pentarou was replaced by Diskun, the Famicom Disk System mascot, on the title screen, and Donkey Kong Jr. appears in the stands on the right side. The conversion offers several variations of play, including one or two player games, plays to 11 or 21 points, and five levels of difficulty. Additionally, Deuce win conditions do not end at 15 points, but can climb as high as 99 points.</desc>
    <releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Sports</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Smash Ping Pong (Japan) [b].zip</path>
    <name>Smash Ping Pong</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Smash Ping Pong (Japan) [b].png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Smash Ping Pong (Japan) [b].png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Smash Ping Pong simulates the game of ping-pong or table tennis in a remarkably different manner than prior simulations of any variety of tennis. Rather than putting the emphasis on precise control and placement of the paddle in order to return the ball, the emphasis is on timing and strategic control of the ball&apos;s speed and trajectory. The player sees no other on-screen representation of themselves beyond a hand holding a paddle. The hand and the paddle automatically move left and right to match the horizontal position of the ball. Players need only concern themselves with the timing of their paddle swing, and the style of swing to use. Players can choose between three different swings, along with the choice of forehand or backhand. 

The Famicom Disk System conversion was developed by Konami, and published directly by Nintendo as Smash Ping Pong. As a result,Konami&apos;s penguin mascot Pentarou was replaced by Diskun, the Famicom Disk System mascot, on the title screen, and Donkey Kong Jr. appears in the stands on the right side. The conversion offers several variations of play, including one or two player games, plays to 11 or 21 points, and five levels of difficulty. Additionally, Deuce win conditions do not end at 15 points, but can climb as high as 99 points.</desc>
    <releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Sports</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Soccer (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Soccer</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Soccer (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Soccer (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Soccer is an action game for two players or one player against the computer. You can play the game in one of five skill levels, choose from several different teams, and select the amount of time the match will take. Soccer features throw-ins, goal kicks, corner kicks, penalty kicks and an overhead view of the field which scrolls to follow the action.</desc>
    <releasedate>19860221T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Sports, Sports / Soccer</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Super Lode Runner (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Super Lode Runner</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Super Lode Runner (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Super Lode Runner (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Douglas E. Smith&apos;s Lode Runner was introduced to Japan in 1983 on various popular Japanese home computer platforms, including the MSX, Sharp X1, and NEC PC family computers. Hudson Soft licensed the rights to bring the game to Nintendo&apos;s Famicom, and it was released in 1984 as one of the first 3rd party games ever made for the system and it was an incredible hit. Around the same time, Irem licensed the rights to produce an arcade version of Lode Runner which they also released in 1984, along with three other sequels through 1986. These arcade versions made a few tweaks to the original game play, and the final arcade game introduced a two player cooperative mode.

In 1987, Irem decided to package a number of select stages from all four of the arcade games into one title, and released it in disk format for the Famicom Disk System, entitled Super Lode Runner. Though the graphics were not quite as good as the arcade games, they were close, and Irem brought many of the game play changes to Famicom players, including the new two player mode. Irem released a sequel later on that same year. A different version of the game was released for the MSX with the same title.</desc>
    <releasedate>19870305T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Irem</developer>
    <publisher>Irem</publisher>
    <genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Super Lode Runner (Japan) [b].zip</path>
    <name>Super Lode Runner</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Super Lode Runner (Japan) [b].png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Super Lode Runner (Japan) [b].png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Douglas E. Smith&apos;s Lode Runner was introduced to Japan in 1983 on various popular Japanese home computer platforms, including the MSX, Sharp X1, and NEC PC family computers. Hudson Soft licensed the rights to bring the game to Nintendo&apos;s Famicom, and it was released in 1984 as one of the first 3rd party games ever made for the system and it was an incredible hit. Around the same time, Irem licensed the rights to produce an arcade version of Lode Runner which they also released in 1984, along with three other sequels through 1986. These arcade versions made a few tweaks to the original game play, and the final arcade game introduced a two player cooperative mode.

In 1987, Irem decided to package a number of select stages from all four of the arcade games into one title, and released it in disk format for the Famicom Disk System, entitled Super Lode Runner. Though the graphics were not quite as good as the arcade games, they were close, and Irem brought many of the game play changes to Famicom players, including the new two player mode. Irem released a sequel later on that same year. A different version of the game was released for the MSX with the same title.</desc>
    <releasedate>19870305T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Irem</developer>
    <publisher>Irem</publisher>
    <genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Super Lode Runner II (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Super Lode Runner II</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Super Lode Runner II (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Super Lode Runner II (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>The second compilation of levels from Irem&apos;s Lode Runner Arcade series. Developed for the Famicom Disk System, it was never released outside of Japan.
Irem created four Arcade versions of the original Lode Runner, each with a unique set of levels as well as added features like a co-operative mode for two players. For the FDS home versions, Irem compiled several levels from each of these Arcade versions onto one disk. Super Lode Runner II has fewer single-player levels than its predecessor, but contains more co-op levels to make up for it.</desc>
    <releasedate>19870825T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Irem</developer>
    <publisher>Irem</publisher>
    <genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Super Lode Runner II (Japan) (Disk Writer) [b].zip</path>
    <name>Super Lode Runner II</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Super Lode Runner II (Japan) (Disk Writer) [b].png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Super Lode Runner II (Japan) (Disk Writer) [b].png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>The second compilation of levels from Irem&apos;s Lode Runner Arcade series. Developed for the Famicom Disk System, it was never released outside of Japan.
Irem created four Arcade versions of the original Lode Runner, each with a unique set of levels as well as added features like a co-operative mode for two players. For the FDS home versions, Irem compiled several levels from each of these Arcade versions onto one disk. Super Lode Runner II has fewer single-player levels than its predecessor, but contains more co-op levels to make up for it.</desc>
    <releasedate>19870825T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Irem</developer>
    <publisher>Irem</publisher>
    <genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Super Mario Brothers (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Super Mario Bros.</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Super Mario Brothers (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Super Mario Brothers (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Do you have what it takes to save the Mushroom Princess?

You&apos;ll have to think fast and move even faster to complete this quest! The Mushroom Princess is being held captive by the evil Koopa tribe of turtles. It&apos;s up to you to rescue her from the clutches of the Koopa King before time runs out. But it won&apos;t be easy. To get to the princess, you&apos;ll have to climb mountains, cross seas, avoid bottomless pits, fight off turtle soldiers and a host of black magic traps that only a Koopa King can devise. It&apos;s another non-stop adventure from the SUPER MARIO BROTHERS!</desc>
    <releasedate>19860221T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Nintendo</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Platform</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Super Mario Brothers 2 (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Super Mario Bros. 2</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Super Mario Brothers 2 (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Super Mario Brothers 2 (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating>0.6</rating>
    <desc>Originally released in Japan as Super Mario Bros. 2, this game has previously made only brief cameo appearances in the Western hemisphere. Mario fans will appreciate the familiar look and feel of the game, while finding that its updated game play creates an entirely new challenge. No longer content just to wear different-colored overalls, Mario and Luigi also possess different skill sets (Mario can stop quicker, while Luigi can jump higher). In addition to the classic enemies already known to fans worldwide, there are also Poison Mushrooms, backward Warp Zones, and the occasional wind gust (which can help or hinder your progress) to take into account. And if that?s somehow not enough, expert players can go looking for the game?s secret worlds. So get ready to put your Mario skills to the ultimate test, and save the Princess again. Just don?t be surprised if she?s in another castle!</desc>
    <releasedate>19860603T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Nintendo</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Platform</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Tanigawa Kouji no Shougi Shinan II - Meijin heno Michi (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Tanigawa Kouji no Shougi Shinan II : Meijin e no Michi</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Tanigawa Kouji no Shougi Shinan II - Meijin heno Michi (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Tanigawa Kouji no Shougi Shinan II - Meijin heno Michi (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Shogi, a Japanese board game similar to chess, is a board game as popular as Mahjong in Japan. Tanigawa Kouji no Shougi Shinan II - Meijin e no Michi  is the second in a series of instructional Shogi games hosted by then-top tier champion and expert Shogi player Tanigawa Kouji to help improve the player&apos;s game.</desc>
    <releasedate>19871113T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Pony Canyon, Inc.</developer>
    <publisher>Pony Canyon, Inc.</publisher>
    <genre>Strategy, Asiatic board game, Shougi</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Tennis (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Tennis</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Tennis (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Tennis (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>The game features single-player and two-player modes for singles and doubles matches, with either competitive or cooperative gameplay. A computerized opponent&apos;s artificial intelligence can be set to one of five difficulty levels. Mario referees the matches.</desc>
    <releasedate>19860221T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Intelligent Systems Co., Ltd.</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Sports, Sports / Tennis</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/TwinBee (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>TwinBee</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/TwinBee (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/TwinBee (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>TwinBee can be played by up to 2-players simultaneously. The player takes control of a cartoon-like anthropomorphic spacecraft, with Player 1 taking control of TwinBee, the titular ship, while Player 2 controls WinBee. The game controls consists of a joystick and two buttons: one for shooting enemies in the air and the other for dropping bombs to ground enemies (similarly to Xevious).

The player&apos;s primary power-ups are bells that can be uncovered by shooting at the floating clouds where they&apos;re hidden. If the player continues shooting the bell after it appears, it will change into one of four other colors: the regular yellow bells only grant bonus points, the white bell will upgrade the player&apos;s gun into a twin cannon, the blue bell increases the player&apos;s speed (for up to five speed levels), the green bell will allow the player to create image copies of its ship for additional firepower, and the red bell will provide the player&apos;s ship a barrier that allows it to sustain more damage. The green and red bells cannot be combined together. Other power-ups can also be retrieved from ground enemies such as an alternate bell that gives the player&apos;s ship a three-way gun, a star which eliminates all on-screen enemies.

As with other games of the same genre, getting shot by a single enemy bullet will cause the player to lose a life. However, if the bullet only strikes either side of the ship instead, the player&apos;s ship will only lose one of its arms. If the player&apos;s ship loses both arms, it will lose the ability to throw bombs and the player must wait for an ambulance to arrive. The player must navigate their ship to the ambulance to repair their arms. However, if the player&apos;s ship loses both arms for the second time, no ambulance will arrive.

If two players are playing at the same time, they can align their ships vertically or horizontally together to perform more powerful attacks</desc>
    <releasedate>19880311T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Shooter, Shoot&apos;em Up</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/TwinBee (Japan) (Disk Writer).zip</path>
    <name>TwinBee</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/TwinBee (Japan) (Disk Writer).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/TwinBee (Japan) (Disk Writer).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>TwinBee can be played by up to 2-players simultaneously. The player takes control of a cartoon-like anthropomorphic spacecraft, with Player 1 taking control of TwinBee, the titular ship, while Player 2 controls WinBee. The game controls consists of a joystick and two buttons: one for shooting enemies in the air and the other for dropping bombs to ground enemies (similarly to Xevious).

The player&apos;s primary power-ups are bells that can be uncovered by shooting at the floating clouds where they&apos;re hidden. If the player continues shooting the bell after it appears, it will change into one of four other colors: the regular yellow bells only grant bonus points, the white bell will upgrade the player&apos;s gun into a twin cannon, the blue bell increases the player&apos;s speed (for up to five speed levels), the green bell will allow the player to create image copies of its ship for additional firepower, and the red bell will provide the player&apos;s ship a barrier that allows it to sustain more damage. The green and red bells cannot be combined together. Other power-ups can also be retrieved from ground enemies such as an alternate bell that gives the player&apos;s ship a three-way gun, a star which eliminates all on-screen enemies.

As with other games of the same genre, getting shot by a single enemy bullet will cause the player to lose a life. However, if the bullet only strikes either side of the ship instead, the player&apos;s ship will only lose one of its arms. If the player&apos;s ship loses both arms, it will lose the ability to throw bombs and the player must wait for an ambulance to arrive. The player must navigate their ship to the ambulance to repair their arms. However, if the player&apos;s ship loses both arms for the second time, no ambulance will arrive.

If two players are playing at the same time, they can align their ships vertically or horizontally together to perform more powerful attacks</desc>
    <releasedate>19880311T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Shooter, Shoot&apos;em Up</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Vs. Excitebike (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Vs. Excitebike</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Vs. Excitebike (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Vs. Excitebike (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Vs. Excitebike is a motorcross racing simulation game developed by Nintendo as a sequel to Excitebike for the Famicom Disk System. It was also released in the arcades but the Famicom Disk System is arguably better with additional features.  It comes with some improved features, including a simultaneous two player mode that the original game lacked, and an improved track save system (the tracks were saved to the writable portion of the disk). The music is completely different; none of the songs from the original game are present in this version, and a background theme is played during gameplay. There is also a new bonus round that has you jumping over trucks.</desc>
    <releasedate>19881209T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Nintendo</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Race, Driving / Motorcycle, Race, Driving</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Yume Koujou Doki Doki Panic (Japan) [b].zip</path>
    <name>Yume Koujou Doki Doki Panic</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Yume Koujou Doki Doki Panic (Japan) [b].png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Yume Koujou Doki Doki Panic (Japan) [b].png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Yume Koujou Doki Doki Panic  (translated as &quot;Dream Factory: Heart-Pounding Panic&quot;) is a Japan-only video game developed by Nintendo in cooperation with Fuji Television for the Family Computer Disk System to promote its event called Yume Koujou &apos;87 (translates to Dream Factory &apos;87).

It was later released outside of Japan in an altered format under the name Super Mario Bros. 2, since the original Japanese Super Mario Bros. sequel, Super Mario Bros.: The Lost Levels, was deemed too similar to the original and too difficult for overseas players. Eventually, the altered Mario version of Doki Doki Panic was released in Japan as well, under the title Super Mario USA. 

The story starts with two chidren, the young twins Piki and Poki, peacefully reading a story book. However, they accidentally tear off the last page of the book - little did they know that the book is actually magic! The evil Mamu suddenly appears, and his huge three-fingered hand pulls them into a quirky dream world. 

The goal of Doki Doki Panic is to help the whole family (namely Imajin, Lina and their parents Mama and Papa) rescue their poor children kidnaped by the evil king lizard. Each member has its own strengths and weaknesses - Imaji is a balanced character whereas Lina is fairly light weight and can effortlessly hover and fly over short distances, but she is really slow at picking up items. Papa is the strongest of the group and can throw enemies and items really far, whereas Mama can jump higher than anyone. As aforementioned, each character can carry enemies, items, and especially radishes and other vegetables that can be pulled out of the ground and used as lethal weapons. The game features a myriad of other items, such as bombs (self explanatory), Power blocks (similar to Mario Bros&apos;s POW blocks that kill all enemies on screen), Stars (temporary invincibility), keys (to unlock doors), Hearts (extra health) or the mysterious magic lamps that open doors to the Dark World - mirror areas where our heroes can find special items or heart containers. 

Doki Doki Panic follows a story book structure, and is made out of seven chapters (areas) and twenty pages (levels). Interestingly, although the player can play the Doki Doki Panic with any character, it has to eventually defeat the evil Mamu with all four to finally beat the game (the player can separately save each character&apos;s progress).</desc>
    <releasedate>19870710T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Nintendo</developer>
    <publisher>Fuji Television Network</publisher>
    <genre>Platform</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Yuu Maze (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Yuu Maze</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Yuu Maze (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Yuu Maze (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Yuu Maze (&quot;Maze Play&quot;) is a single-screen maze game akin to Namco&apos;s classic Pac-Man and its many other imitators in that the goal of the game is to drive the futuristic vehicle around a maze collecting dots while avoiding (or temporarily eliminating) the enemies. Taito, one of the largest manufacturers of Arcade games at the time (not to mention the creators of Space Invaders), would produce similarly Arcade-reminiscent games for the system in order to tap into the portion of the market nostalgic for classic Arcade experiences.Yuu Maze adds a few innovations to the format: Each maze has a different structure, different enemies and different lay-outs for the pellets that are required to complete the level; the player can find power-ups which grant weapons, shields and speed-ups to their vehicle. The player&apos;s vehicle also has some degree of inertia: There&apos;s a slight delay when attempting to accelerate after stopping or performing a U-turn, but if the player keeps moving and changes direction only at 90 degree intervals, they can keep moving at their maximum speed. This is often necessary to keep ahead of the fast moving enemies.</desc>
    <releasedate>19881028T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Daiei Seisakusho</developer>
    <publisher>Taito</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Zatsugaku Olympic Quiz Part II (Japan) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Zatsugaku Olympic Quiz Part II</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Zatsugaku Olympic Quiz Part II (Japan) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Zatsugaku Olympic Quiz Part II (Japan) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>An adult game in which answering various quiz questions correctly within a time limit will slowly remove panels from a picture that usually reveal a nude girl.</desc>
    <releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Phoenix</developer>
    <publisher>Phoenix</publisher>
    <genre>Quiz, Adult</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Zelda no Densetsu - The Hyrule Fantasy (Japan) (v1.1).zip</path>
    <name>Zelda no Densetsu : The Hyrule Fantasy</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Zelda no Densetsu - The Hyrule Fantasy (Japan) (v1.1).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Zelda no Densetsu - The Hyrule Fantasy (Japan) (v1.1).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>A small kingdom in the land of Hyrule, the setting of the game, is engulfed in chaos after an army led by Ganon, the Prince of Darkness, invaded it and stole the Triforce of Power, a part of a magical artifact bestowing great strength. In an attempt to prevent Ganon from acquiring the Triforce of Wisdom, another of the pieces, Princess Zelda splits it and hides the eight fragments in secret dungeons throughout the land. Before the princess is eventually kidnapped by Ganon, she commands her nursemaid Impa to find someone courageous enough to save the kingdom. While wandering the land, the old woman is surrounded by Ganon&apos;s henchmen, though a young boy named Link appears and rescues her.  After hearing Impa&apos;s plea, he resolves to save Zelda and sets out to reassemble the scattered fragments of the Triforce of Wisdom, to become powerful enough to defeat Ganon.

The Legend of Zelda incorporates elements of action, adventure, and role-playing games. The player controls Link from a flip-screen overhead perspective as he travels in the overworld, a large outdoor map with varied environments. Link begins the game armed only with a small shield, but a sword becomes available to Link after he ventures into a cave that is accessible from the game&apos;s first map screen. Throughout the game, various characters aid Link by giving or selling equipment and clues. These people can be found in caves scattered throughout the overworld; some are readily accessible, while others are hidden behind obstacles such as rocks, trees, and waterfalls

Nintendo originally released the game as the launch title for the Family Computer&apos;s new Disk System peripheral. The Legend of Zelda was joined by a re-release of Super Mario Bros., Tennis, Baseball, Golf, Soccer, and Mahjong in its introduction of the Disk System. It made full use of the Disk Card media&apos;s advantages over traditional ROM cartridges with a disk size of 128 kilobytes, which was expensive to produce on cartridge format. Due to the still-limited amount of space on the disk, however, it was only in katakana. Rather than passwords, it used rewritable disks to save the game. It used the extra sound channel provided by the Disk System for certain sound effects; most notable are the sounds of Link&apos;s sword when his health is full, the roars and growls of dungeon bosses, and enemy death sounds. The sound effects used the Famicom&apos;s PCM channel in the cartridge version. It also used the microphone built into the Famicom&apos;s controller that</desc>
    <releasedate>19860221T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Nintendo</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Adventure</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/pi/RetroPie/roms/fds/Zelda no Densetsu - The Hyrule Fantasy (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Zelda no Densetsu : The Hyrule Fantasy</name>
    <cover />
    <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/screenshots/Zelda no Densetsu - The Hyrule Fantasy (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_media/fds/marquees/Zelda no Densetsu - The Hyrule Fantasy (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>A small kingdom in the land of Hyrule, the setting of the game, is engulfed in chaos after an army led by Ganon, the Prince of Darkness, invaded it and stole the Triforce of Power, a part of a magical artifact bestowing great strength. In an attempt to prevent Ganon from acquiring the Triforce of Wisdom, another of the pieces, Princess Zelda splits it and hides the eight fragments in secret dungeons throughout the land. Before the princess is eventually kidnapped by Ganon, she commands her nursemaid Impa to find someone courageous enough to save the kingdom. While wandering the land, the old woman is surrounded by Ganon&apos;s henchmen, though a young boy named Link appears and rescues her.  After hearing Impa&apos;s plea, he resolves to save Zelda and sets out to reassemble the scattered fragments of the Triforce of Wisdom, to become powerful enough to defeat Ganon.

The Legend of Zelda incorporates elements of action, adventure, and role-playing games. The player controls Link from a flip-screen overhead perspective as he travels in the overworld, a large outdoor map with varied environments. Link begins the game armed only with a small shield, but a sword becomes available to Link after he ventures into a cave that is accessible from the game&apos;s first map screen. Throughout the game, various characters aid Link by giving or selling equipment and clues. These people can be found in caves scattered throughout the overworld; some are readily accessible, while others are hidden behind obstacles such as rocks, trees, and waterfalls

Nintendo originally released the game as the launch title for the Family Computer&apos;s new Disk System peripheral. The Legend of Zelda was joined by a re-release of Super Mario Bros., Tennis, Baseball, Golf, Soccer, and Mahjong in its introduction of the Disk System. It made full use of the Disk Card media&apos;s advantages over traditional ROM cartridges with a disk size of 128 kilobytes, which was expensive to produce on cartridge format. Due to the still-limited amount of space on the disk, however, it was only in katakana. Rather than passwords, it used rewritable disks to save the game. It used the extra sound channel provided by the Disk System for certain sound effects; most notable are the sounds of Link&apos;s sword when his health is full, the roars and growls of dungeon bosses, and enemy death sounds. The sound effects used the Famicom&apos;s PCM channel in the cartridge version. It also used the microphone built into the Famicom&apos;s controller that</desc>
    <releasedate>19860221T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Nintendo</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Adventure</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
</gameList>